Previously on "Yellowstone"
I don't need your permission
to assemble.
This isn't for assembling.
This is greeting the President
of the United States.
He's going to endorse Martin.
And don't you ever
call this work!
Governor of Montana
on the side of a mountain.
sleeping with his boots on.
Couldn't have dreamed up
a better death if you paid me.
I can't have Emmett's wife
watch the herd ride in
without him. and no answers.
How?
Like a cowboy should.
Just trying figure out.
what you're doing here?
Here's my ulterior motive.
Do you wanna hear it?
Get you elected governor
and save this state.
One for the road?
Are you stupid enough
to ask me for that
in front of my father?
Be careful.
Careful don't factor
too much into this.
See you when you get back.
You know. I've done some
stupid shit in my life.
but this tops it.
I mean. how the hell are we
supposed to keep wolves
from coming after 5.000 calves?
You ain't gonna stop nothing
sitting by that fire.
I'm gonna ride through 'em.
Yeah. great.
Go save the day. cowboy.
You know. I could be holding
that girl's ass
in each hand.
but no...
I'm sitting here in
a sage brush with you.
What girl?
What do you mean. what girl?
The one you couldn't keep.
What are you gonna do.
half pint?
You never mention her name.
You don't touch her.
You don't fucking talk
to her. you understand?
Try to stab me.
you fucking coward?
Try it again and I will shoot
you where you stand.
Here.
You should drink some water.
It hurts... Head's spinning.
Maybe next time you won't
pull a knife in a fist fight.
Here. try to drink something.
I'm hurt bad.
You need to go to the hospital?
I think so.
- Can you ride?
- Yeah.
I'll go get help.
Tell 'em I fell off my horse
and he trampled me.
Or you'll get in
a lot of trouble.
Rowdy's hurt. Hurt bad.
Where is he?
With the cattle.
Hurt too bad to ride he says.
He get bucked off?
Rip. did he get bucked off?
No sir. he talked
about your daughter
in a way he shouldn't
and we fought about it.
He pulled his knife and I hit
him in the head with a rock.
Too hard. I guess...
You wait here.
Here. give it to me.
Here you go.
- He's dead.
- He's dead?
That ain't gonna help.
Get down off that horse.
Why didn't you just tell me
he fell off his horse?
That's what Rowdy said.
You said never lie to you
so. I didn't.
Well. you're
gonna have to lie now.
Or you're going to prison. son.
Rowdy ain't got no family.
He's just a drifter.
We could drop him off
at the train station.
That's putting a lot
of trust in this boy.
Boy's putting a
fair amount in us. too.
Quit fucking crying.
The time to worry
about consequences
was before the fight.
There's a thing I could do.
but if I do it. you don't
ever leave this place.
You'll be part of this ranch
until the day you die.
and you will do for
this ranch what I say do.
No matter what that is...
you understand me?
This ranch is
the only family I've got.
Ain't ever leaving it
no matter what you do.
All right.
Come help me.
This was not what
I was supposed to be.
I was... I was...
I was raised to be a cowboy.
To... to run a ranch. To...
To know the nuances
of being a cattle producer.
To... You know. from. from...
from understanding
the grass cycles.
to... to timing
the calving season
to maximize the grass cycles.
Understanding bull genetics
and diseases.
It was...
I never wanted to be
a fucking lawyer.
This is what he wanted me to be.
What he thought he needed.
"The future of warfare
is fought with a pen.
Learn to fight with a pen."
All right. So. I did.
And I did.
And then I get this acceptance
letter from Harvard.
Hell. I never even applied.
He applied for me.
There's no telling who
wrote the fucking essay.
Your sister. I would think.
Never thought of that.
God. why didn't I think of that?
Because you're too close to it.
My father hates me.
Hates me.
He hates me for
becoming the very thing
he asked me to become.
No. forced me to be.
Do you care that he hates you?
Is his love something
you feel you really need?
Evidently not. I've lived
without it my whole life.
But I would like his approval.
I want his appreciation
for that fucking sacrifice.
He can't give you that.
He resents the tool
that he relies on the most.
because he can't be that tool.
He's jealous of you. Jamie.
And he's scared of you.
He's scared because
the future of that ranch
depends on its evolution.
If it doesn't evolve
with society
it will be devoured by society
I know. I know.
I've said that for years.
Decades.
And he's still running
cow-calf pairs
like it's the 1950s. when
cow-calf pairs in the 1950s
didn't even make any money.
Cattle.
Let me tell you the future
of the cattle industry.
Right now. the biggest
meat processor
in the United States
is a Brazilian Corporation.
10.000 acres of rainforest
cleared every day.
For what? To raise cattle.
Is that a coincidence?
The future of the beef industry
in the United States
- is no future.
- Mm-mm.
In twenty years Brazil
will be to American beef
what China is to
American manufacturing.
There will be no
more cattle in America.
That's why
the airport development
was vital to the ranch's future.
You don't have to tell me that.
Mm-mm.
But you do have to tell
the rest of Montana.
Tourism is Montana's
only resource.
What else do you have. timber?
Cutting down something it
takes 200 years to replace?
That is not a business.
That is self mutilation.
No. Tourism.
That is all you have.
And you can seize it
or you can witness it.
Those are your options.
I know.
You love that ranch.
It's the only thing
I've ever loved.
Let me help you save it.
I can help you save it
if you want me to.
I do.
Ask me. then.
Ask me to help you save it.
Will you help me?
Help me.
I will help you. baby.
Mmm.
♪ Mountain. mountain ♪
♪ It's good to see your face ♪
♪ Mighty wonder ♪
♪ High above the plains ♪
♪ Mountain. mountain ♪
♪ Could I take your place? ♪
♪ River. river ♪
♪ Take me away ♪
♪ Wash me clean ♪
♪ Keep my sins at bay ♪
Morning.
We'll be back by noon.
That's usually when I wake up.
And now you're just leavin'.
This job starts early.
I feel so used.
Yeah? That's exactly how I feel.
I'll see you later.
♪ Carrying with me
Everything I own and who I am ♪
♪ Pray to God
I see your face agin ♪
I'm gonna go back to sleep.
Okay.
You'd better be worth
this walk of shame.
Half my church
is camped out here.
♪ Stars are burnin' ♪
♪ Up in the sky ♪
♪ Celestial angels
Teach me who to fly ♪
♪ Stars are burnin' ♪
♪ Won't you take me on high ♪
♪ Take me on high ♪
♪ Pine tree campfire
End of the night ♪
♪ Embers burnin'
Shedding you light ♪
♪ Bottle of Blanton's
Got me feelin' right ♪
Hey.
I'm not sad. I'm... I'm happy.
You're becoming a man. Tate.
Watching that makes me happy.
You don't have to get up. baby.
Oh. we got a lot
of mouths to feed.
Why don't we give your mom
some privacy. okay?
All right.
- Bye. Mom.
- Bye. baby.
Thanks. Gator.
Thank you. Gator.
Go. boys.
Morning. sir. Morning.
This is my favorite part.
Of everything we do. this is...
this is my favorite.
Well. I prefer when it's done.
And everything went smooth.
That part just makes me
sad it's over.
- Morning.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Look at all you sluts.
You're sitting here. too.
I doubt you just wandered down
from the house
to take in the view.
Yeah. well. I'm a married woman.
- But you tramps...
- Ah. yes.
That arcane ritual
where you stand
before family and friends
and swear before God deity
that you will surrender
your independence
and obey the man you are
betrothed to.
Betrothed?
See. what Summer's
is attempting to do here
is make out that marriage
is designed to somehow
oppress and control a woman.
You know. if you married to
a piece of shit. it can be.
but if you married the love
of your life.
the mirror to your soul.
it's pretty fucking great.
I thought we agreed
to get along.
We did. I didn't agree
to placate
some of your hippie bullshit
where every institution
and every custom
is designed to oppress.
They are.
They are what you make em. babe.
I'm going to get a shower.
You could probably use one.
- Are there showers here?
- Yeah. in the bunkhouse.
I'll show you.
What?
Just waiting for another zinger.
I'm all zinged out for now.
Why are you so mean?
No reason.
It's fun.
That's fun for you?
What. to point out the very
thing that everyone's thinking
but they don't have the spine
to own it and say?
"Yeah. damn right I romped
in the tent all night.
"You should try it." Which I did.
Most of the night.
Yes. I find that amusing.
Well. I think it's cruel.
Well. that's why I don't
do it to you.
Those cowgirls. they give
as good as they get
and that patchouli-scented
know it all. well. she needs it.
You don't need it.
Well. I don't need to
be treated differently
just because I lost a child.
Yeah. you do.
I'm gonna tell you something...
I haven't told anybody so.
let's keep this between us.
Okay.
I know how you feel
because I've felt it.
And I feel it every day.
So when I say that
I am sorry. Monica...
I really mean it.
Thank you.
That's why you're mean.
Because nobody knows.
Because you keep
that inside yourself.
I keep it inside because of...
all the people knowing it
would hurt.
Anyway. that's not why I'm mean.
I was a real fucking bitch
before it happened. so...
Well... You're very good at it.
I try.
Chairman Rainwater.
right this way.
Chairman Rainwater is here.
Thanks.
- Tom.
- Senator.
Thanks for coming.
Please. sit.
Either of you like coffee?
Well. I'm too curious
for coffee.
Well. I'll get
right to it. then.
The Department of Interior
has approved
two pipelines
in central Montana.
One is a natural gas. and
the other is captured carbon
and the proposed pathway
is through the reservation.
The Secretary of the Interior
was here
with the President two days ago.
They mentioned nothing.
As I'm learning.
Federal politics is. well.
they never take the gloves off
because they never put them on.
Is there a map of this pathway?
The pipeline runs
beneath our reservoir.
Yes.
Our drinking water.
How is the path chosen?
Well. it's the
shortest distance between
two points and the path
of least legal resistance.
To go to the west of you enters
into State land forest service.
east of you is private ranches.
which have the funds to fight.
and likely the support
of our new governor.
They don't think
we'll put up a fight?
We can't put up a fight.
Federal Government doesn't
need our permission.
So that my position is clear.
I do not support this.
And I will declare
my opposition.
how much weight that holds
in this instance... I...
If there's nothing you can do
and there's nothing I can do.
why are you telling me?
Because I know who's
coming after your office
and they'll use
this against you.
At least now. make a statement.
get out in front of it.
Make enough noise that
the Department of Interior
looks somewhere else.
North Dakota. let's say.
That just ruins the land
in North Dakota.
I'm not the Senator
of North Dakota.
So that's
North Dakota's problem.
I guess you don't
put gloves on either.
When will you publicly
declare your opposition?
As soon as the pipeline
is made public.
which I assume is when
you'll call a press conference.
You set the press conference.
Stand with the people
this affects.
Standing beside you
in solidarity
is declaring my support for you
as much as it is
opposing a pipeline.
We'll kill two birds
with one stone.
Deal.
I'll set it for tomorrow.
Be good to have
the governor there.
Well. the governor's
playing hooky.
Branding cattle.
That's not what
he was elected to do.
Oh. he did what
That's the way John
sees it. anyway.
He's our governor. too.
Perhaps you could remind
him of that.
Hup. hup.
Sh-sh-sh-sh...
Damn. Lloyd.
What?
That's the third one I've seen.
- One what?
- Stillborn buffalo calf.
- Where?
- Just right back there.
Aw. shit. this ain't
gonna be good.
Buffalo from the park
been in this pasture.
Found two dead bison calves
there. stillborn.
Walker said he's
seen two more of 'em.
Let me guess.
you found a stillborn bison.
Two.
Why would that happen?
Brucellosis. Clara.
Found something
you're going to want to see.
We found it. too.
Can cattle get it?
Yes. cattle can get it.
Well. how can you tell?
Well. we'll test them for it.
And if one cow has it. the state
destroys the whole herd.
All our cows have calves.
We're not going to solve
this on the side of the hill.
Let's get em to headquarters.
We'll figure it out there.
♪ Gonna cast
A long black shadow ♪
♪ Over you and
All white chapel ♪
- Open her up.
- ♪ And a silver dagger ♪
♪ Nobody gonna
Hear you shatter ♪
♪ Bad moon rising overhead ♪
♪ Bad blood running
through my head ♪
♪ Little mama
You sure look fine ♪
♪ But you're sleeping
On your own tonight ♪
♪ Yeah you're sleeping
Good cut. Jake. Good job. buddy.
♪ All saints. all sinners ♪
Just push it in. Simple job.
- That'll do.
- All right. boys. good job.
Let's go ahead
and push them up the chute.
Hep. hep. hep.
Yeah. that's all the cows.
♪ Good to let it out ♪
♪ Little mama's baby boy ♪
♪ Little mama.
You're my pride and joy ♪
♪ Wanna put you out on display ♪
♪ Little mama. I'm on my way ♪
Whatever's left. we're going
to brand and castrate.
♪ Little mama. I'm on my way ♪
♪ All saints. all sinners ♪
Here you go.
♪ All the same ♪
Woo! You jumping in on this?
You doing it? Yep.
- Oh. yeah.
- All right. come on.
Ready? Right.
Right side on one. two. three.
Get him over good.
- Got him?
- Yep.
Great. man. look at
the fuckin' girl power.
Gun powder? For what?
Girl power.
Fucking girl power. man!
You speak fucking English?
What the fuck are you saying?
- Fuck it.
- Just do it!
Come on. little miss sunshine.
I'm so fucking
sorry. little calf.
It's for your own good
so you don't get sick.
I'm sorry. I'm so fucking sorry.
Sorry. sorry.
I feel like I shouldn't be
watching. but I can't stop.
It's riveting.
This is so fucking traumatizing.
We're up.
♪ All saints. all sinners ♪
You tell me when
you're ready for me.
- Oh my God!
- We're ready.
Yeah. okay.
Oh. this is fucking traumatizing.
Ooh hoo hoo!
You ever seen one with blackleg?
- No.
- That's traumatizing.
You are doing
the calf a big favor.
And if you could do
that favor a little faster.
- Okay.
- Come on!
I'm sorry. little calf.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
- Okay. set?
- Yep.
If the state kills the herd.
do they pay you back?
Not what it's worth.
The herd's insured but...
I don't know.
I don't know how we rebuild
a hundred years of genetics.
Look. if one of
them tests positive.
there's nothing we can do.
Start over. I guess.
But if they don't.
we got a bigger problem.
We can't use that south pasture.
There's fifty miles
of fence to check.
that lower valley's too dry.
they got nothing to eat.
We wean early. send the calves
to a back grounding yard
in Nebraska. or...
The trucking will
kill us. Kayce.
and we're already paying
a gain on top of it.
What about hayin' 'em?
Yeah. and feed em
with what in the winter?
Son of a bitch.
Look. I'll. um...
I'll start making some calls.
Find us some lease ground.
To make this pencil out
half the herd needs to go
and it needs to stay
a year or more.
Lease ground where?
Somewhere with a mild winter.
If half the herd goes.
who watches 'em?
Who do you think. Kayce?
Lloyd.
Well. what's the plan?
Mister Dutton
wants to lease land down south
and get the herd out.
I'll go with the herd.
Who else you gonna take?
I don't know.
Who you want to stay here?
Hell. you're the one living
out of a teepee in new country.
you take who you want.
All right.
I'll go with Jake.
Teeter. Ryan...
and hell. I'll take Walker.
You ain't gonna kill him
out there on the plains
somewhere. are you?
We're probably going
to his old stomping ground.
I might need someone that
knows some folks down there.
By the way.
I'm more fucking worried
about you killing his ass.
My memory's not as
mean as yours.
You're gonna be a long
way from home.
Long way from your wife.
I ain't got nobody.
you oughta send me.
I'm ranch manager. Lloyd.
It's my responsibility.
I appreciate it. though.
Well. when you are you leaving?
Soon as Mr. Dutton
signs the lease
and I get the trucks lined up.
- You're gonna need Gator.
- Go tell him. will ya?
Jake. Walker.
Ryan. Teeter.
Get over here.
All right. listen up.
After we brand these cattle.
we're going to hold them here.
then we're gonna
put them on trucks.
we're going to take them
to lease ground.
You four are coming with me.
We're gonna get some day workers
when we get down there.
- Where?
- I don't know.
Somewhere where it doesn't
snow in the winter.
Go and pack up
everything you got.
Your teepees. all of it.
We'll be gone for a while.
What are you smiling about?
Gonna go do some
cowboy shit now.
You keep that bunkhouse
and cable TV.
Thanks for picking us. boss.
- Yes. sir.
- Thank you. sir.
You got it.
Ryan.
I want you to tell me right now
if this is going
to be a problem.
I don't want to hear about it
in some canyon in New Mexico.
There's nothin' I'd rather do.
Sir. thank you for the chance.
You got it.
Ryan. Ryan. hold on a second.
Why don't you take
the bunkhouse to the fair.
You go have some fun.
You ain't gonna see
a town in a long while.
Thank you.
That's Swarovski crystal. Dad.
Swarovski makes optics. honey.
With the glass from their
crystal factory.
Yeah. well. I need
to break something.
That is a hundred years old
and belonged
to your grandfather.
Break something else.
Need to move our herd
down south.
Buffalo herd left the park.
Spent spring on our ranch.
Herd has brucellosis now.
That sounds ominous.
It is.
How far south?
Far enough that it doesn't snow.
so we don't have
to feed them all winter.
Okay. so do you
have to lease the land?
- Yeah.
- And how much will that cost?
Dry as it is? I don't know.
12. 14 dollars an acre.
Okay. how many acres?
Depends on the land.
Hundred thousand at least.
So that's
1.4 million dollars a year.
No. Beth.
1.4 a month.
Dad. we don't...
We don't have that.
I know. I'll take a loan.
Why don't you
just sell them all now?
If we sell 'em all now.
we have no income next year.
We don't have any
income this year.
We have no profit this year.
We have no profit any year.
Now I want to break shit.
If we sell the heifers and
the steers. what is that worth?
If I can get them to weigh
750. worth about 1100 dollars.
Okay. so that's
a $1.50 a pound. Dad.
Yep.
A good steak is worth
thirty bucks a pound.
shitty ground beef
is worth five.
We don't sell beef.
we sell cattle.
Exactly. We're in the wrong
fucking business.
You know. I really. uh...
I really thought the airport
would be the end of us. Dad. but...
Your business model.
is gonna be the end of us.
Business model's
worked for a hundred years...
No. Dad. it hasn't worked.
If it worked. this fucking
valley wouldn't be filled
with hobby farms
and vacation houses.
It would be filled with ranches.
People don't sell businesses
that make money. right?
They sell the losers.
Randy. John Dutton. How are ya?
You all stocked up?
Yeah. I need some ground.
Five thousand
if I can find the grass.
Yeah. I know him.
Who else if that doesn't work?
Oh. um. Ellis Steele is in
your office with Miss Atwood.
Sarah?
That's weird.
Can I say something. that's...
That I don't have
a right to say?
Sure?
Women know women.
Men know what a woman
wants them to know.
I worry about
you being with her.
Oh. I'm not...
Who told you I was with her?
You're with her.
Thank you for saying something.
I'll keep it in mind.
This is...
Unexpected.
Um...
What's on your mind. Mr. Steele?
This.
Your father put his ranch
in the Land Trust.
He put the land in a
conservation easement. Jamie.
How could you let him do that?
Well. I...
I...
I didn't know.
Do you have the authority
to override that?
Theoretically. yes.
But...
You're not battling
a man. anymore.
you're battling the legal
defense funds
of environmental groups.
which had no basis to sue you.
but now they are
the stewards of the...
Fuck!
God damn it!
Thank you for coming.
I'm going to need some time
to process this information.
Market Equity will sue the state
for a bad faith negotiation.
They will file it in
federal court in New York.
where they incurred the damages.
and those attorneys will
wipe the floor with you.
Your state will be on the hook
for around 4 billion dollars
in compensatory damages.
That's ten percent
of Montana's GDP.
The state's gonna go bankrupt.
Sounds like an
impeachable offense to me.
Yes. it does.
What's the procedure in Montana
when a Governor resigns
or steps down?
You have a special election.
We're fully committed
to your election.
Our PAC will fund it.
Go before the Assembly.
This is your chance
to become governor...
and get our fucking land back.
Supply House.
Is this the number
to order beef?
Yes. ma'am.
or you can do it online.
Can I be nosey?
Umm. sure.
Is this your beef. that you
raise and sell online?
Yes. ma'am. Some comes
from neighboring ranchers
'cause we sell out of all ours.
but they follow
the same program.
You sell out?
Yes. ma'am.
How many pounds
of beef do you raise?
This year. a little
over 8 million.
What's the catch?
Ma'am?
There's always a catch.
No catch.
You just gotta have enough
money to feed your herd
for two years before
you make any money.
Or get a big loan.
And have a lot
of backbone. ma'am.
Backbone we got. thank you.
Joe. I can't thank you enough.
Once I get the trucks lined up
I'll start sending 'em your way.
This is what you
get your loan for.
The cash flow
is impossible. honey.
and nobody can figure
out the packer.
They figured out the packer.
Do you know this ranch?
Yeah. I was just on
the phone with this ranch.
So was I.
They sold 8 million
pounds of beef.
On a website.
I don't know what their
arrangement is honey.
but one thing I do know is...
nobody has ever been able
to figure out the re-packer.
That is because you are not
a businessman. Daddy.
You are a rancher.
I am a businessman.
And I have spent my
career making
fifty. hundred million
dollar deals for others.
Now I'm gonna make one for you.
Sir?
Line up the trucks.
They're lined up.
We just need to know
where they're headed.
Ground in Eastern Colorado and
north of Panhandle in Texas.
Okay. Sweetheart...
Don't bite my head off
for asking this question.
I don't like the way
this is starting.
Me either...
Um... Would you like to come
to the fair with me?
Sure. when?
Yes? Really?
Yeah. why wouldn't I want
to go to the fair?
Is fair some sort of metaphor
for something a father
shouldn't be hearing?
No. no. It's the fair.
It's the county fair.
It's been happening
for the last 92 years. sir.
- I'll get my sweater.
- Okay. sweetie.
So. you're talking
about going to the fair.
Yes. sir. Yeah.
Yeah. that's a great idea.
Carter. go on and get washed up.
We're going to go to the fair.
Come on.
How long you gonna be gone?
Well. until we don't want to
be there. What do you mean?
I mean down south.
A while.
How long's a while?
I don't know. son.
Now go on. Get washed up.
♪ It's the motorcycle Drive-by ♪
♪ Baby dry your kind eyes ♪
♪ I think it's about
Time we headed home ♪
♪ Walking on such tight rope ♪
♪ With my damn high hopes ♪
♪ Country boys Don't die alone ♪
♪ Every day's so fleeting ♪
♪ And I have been trying ♪
♪ To save it while I can ♪
♪ Look on her face
All these hot humid days ♪
♪ And the boys in My damn band ♪
♪ It's the motorcycle Drive-by ♪
♪ Baby dry your kind eyes ♪
♪ I think it's about time
We headed home ♪
♪ Walking such tight rope ♪
♪ With my damn high hopes ♪
♪ Country boys don't die alone ♪
Hey. Are you alright with
people taking our picture?
You're my environmental
advisor. all right?
Try to resist the temptation
to jump my bones
and we'll be all right.
I'll see if I can
control myself.
You do that.
There he is.
You're good.
Thanks.
What?
Nuthin'.
Wanna go see the band?
You bet.
Tate. honey. why don't
you stay with Carter. okay?
All right.
Can we have more money?
Make it last.
Make it last?
A hot dog here is nine dollars.
Thanks.
Think we reached the point
where we're just
a bank and a taxi.
Before you know it.
he'll be the taxi.
Hey. He's about to win me
a fuckin' bar.
Let's go. right here.
Right here. I want
that fuckin' bar.
That fuckin' bar right there.
All these games are rigged.
Who gives a shit? I want it!
Why don't I just give you
the thirty dollars
it's gonna cost me
to win the bear?
Give me the bar. Come on.
Hi. what's up?
Can you explain this game to me?
All you gotta do is
toss three balls
in the center hole.
you can take your prize.
- All right.
- Sounds delightful.
You get it in
the hole all the time at home.
- Let's do it just like home.
- There's kids around. relax.
You got this. baby. Come on.
Just throw it.
Holy fuck. that just went in.
That went in?
Yes. sir. Right in.
Okay. but. nobody gets
two in a row.
so it doesn't really matter...
Whatever. you want to step
closer and get me my bar. let's go.
Give me two more of those.
Right in!
Fuck yeah!
- That went in?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay wait. so. if I get this...
then I win?
Yes. sir.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Don't start trying now.
Just throw it like
you been throwing it.
Yeah. but I haven't even
been looking.
Then don't look.
Right here. you just do
that same thing again.
- Fuck it.
- Right here.
Woo! Fuck yeah. baby!
Mama gonna be so good tonight.
There's kids around!
Give me my bar.
Come on. man. you give me
my fuckin' bar.
- She wants the bear.
That's what I said.
I love my bar!
♪ The sun set so late tonight ♪
♪ I wonder if you saw it. too ♪
♪ Wish I still had
Someone to lose ♪
♪ All I got are these
Summertime blues ♪
♪ Bet there's a green-eyed
Dark haired beauty ♪
♪ On some beach by Monterey ♪
♪ Lettin' waves
Wash her pain away ♪
♪ But I'll never know ♪
♪ Bet there's some boys
Out in okie ♪
How long will you be gone?
I don't know.
Well. ball-park it.
- Maybe a year.
- A year?
Honey. I can't live
without you for a year.
Beth. I know it's gonna
be tough.
No. I mean it.
I won't survive that.
You wanna live in a canvas tent?
For a year?
Take a fuckin' shower once
a week in a Motel 6?
Come on now.
Well we swore to spend
our lives together.
Where you go. I go.
I'm gonna do what the fuck
I wanna do anyway. so...
I'm well aware
of that. sweetheart.
All right. so it's settled.
How long is the drive?
I mean. hauling horses.
I'd say probably 20 hours.
- 20?
- Mm-hm.
How far away
is the nearest city?
Maybe an hour.
All right. well. I'll fly
and meet your ass there.
Listen. the easiest thing
about cowboying is hauling
horses. sweetie.
Well. I'm not doing
any cowboying. You are.
I'm gonna rent a suite
at the nearest Hyatt
and I'll drive to you
for Happy Hour.
Oh. really?
♪ Hauling hay
Fightin' off the sun ♪
♪ Ladies waitin' in town ♪
♪ My summertime blues
Summertime blues ♪
♪ I've got nothing
Left to prove ♪
♪ Out of touch and out of tune ♪
♪ Singin' alone ♪
So how long do you think
y'all gonna be gone for?
Hell. it'll take at least
a year for it to pencil out.
You're going
to Texas for a year?
You didn't care to mention that?
We just found out today.
Abby.
♪ I've got nothing
Left to prove ♪
Abby?
Abby!
♪ To the birds up high
And the souls below ♪
Abby.
- Abigail.
- Did you quit your job?
Why would I do that?
Did you demand to stay
on the ranch here?
I'm sure someone is...
Look. I don't see the point
in you running after me
if you don't have something
different to tell me.
- Abby. you don't understand...
- Then explain it to me.
- You sing in the shower?
- I sing everywhere.
Mm-hm.
Cowboying. That's how I sing.
If the Grand Ol' Oprey
is your Super Bowl.
then moving five thousand head
to land we don't know
and keeping that herd together.
and protectin' them
through winter.
and new predators and
new diseases. that's mine.
♪ To the birds up high
And the souls below ♪
♪ All those boys
Who ain't got no home ♪
♪ The beautiful girls
I'll never hold ♪
♪ This one's for you ♪
Chasing a dream. I understand.
- And I hope you catch it.
- ♪ My summertime blues ♪
I just wish that dream was me.
♪ Bought a bottle
Of the Best Bourbon ♪
♪ A beat down boy could buy ♪
♪ Gonna bury all my sorrow ♪
♪ As the summertime passes ♪
♪ My summertime blues
Summertime blues ♪
♪ I've got nothing
Left to prove ♪
♪ Out of touch And out of tune ♪
♪ Singing alone ♪
You don't like the band?
Hm?
The band?
Oh. he's... he's good.
- Just...
- You look sad.
You know I look at...
look at all these people...
this is dying.
It's already dead
where you're from.
But now all the people where
you're from are...
coming out here and I can't...
I can't stop it.
Okay.
Have you tried?
Well that's. um...
why I became governor.
You ran for governor to stop
an airport in a subdivision
and you did that it one day.
What I never understood
about you guys
is all you do is bitch
about how much people
move into rural America.
ruin it.
change the culture.
but I've lived all over
the mountain west.
Gunnison. Santa Fe.
Jackson Hole. Telluride.
and not once...
never once...
did my neighbor bring me
to a branding
or the fair.
Or the harvest or whatever
community ritual is happening.
they just glared at my hiking
shorts and my license plate
and judged me.
Same way I judged you.
♪ I've got nothing
Left to prove ♪
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not ordering a steak
for dinner any time soon.
But I understand now.
I understand why you brand
and why you vaccinate
and why move them from one
pasture to another.
Twelve million tourists a year
come to Montana from cities.
You might wanna think about
inviting a few of them over
so they understand
who you really are
and what you really do
because they have you pegged
as a bunch of misogynist bigots
who are ruining the environment
and that is not who you are.
You're a smart woman. Summer.
Very. very smart woman.
I'm a smart person.
Well. women are smarter than men
to begin with so I'm just
judging you against your peers.
Thanks for kidnapping me.
I'm really enjoying it.
I didn't...
I did not kidnap you... I commuted
your sentence to house arrest.
At your house.
I guess in the narrowest
of legal interpretations
maybe...
you're right.
Thanks for doing it.
♪ My summertime blues ♪
As your press advisor I
suggest you postpone that look.
You're my environmental advisor.
My press advisor's
behind me. making out.
♪ Bought a bottle of the best
bourbon a beat down ♪
You have no intention of
running for a second term do you?
Absolutely zero.
What is it about sad songs
and cowboys?
♪ All those boys
Who ain't got no home ♪
I don't care what they think.
You made that abundantly clear.
Well there's no one
in front of us.
Very few to my right
and everyone to my left
is with me.
That just leaves
the 1.500 behind us.
Oh yeah.
Yeah. Well...
I think you're gonna
like this trick.
♪ All I got are these
Summertime Blues ♪
The actions of Governor Dutton
have not only robbed Montanans
of six thousand jobs and
annual revenue in the billions.
his actions have exposed
Montana to litigation
that will cost
the state billions more.
likely bankrupting the state.
Which robs your
children of school funding.
robs our towns
of emergency services.
places our roads and
infrastructure in disrepair.
It threatens the quality
of life for all Montanans.
After weighing his actions
and the cost of those actions
for every Montanan.
I call on this assembly
for a vote to impeach.
Mister Speaker. what say ye?
What do you think?
I think it's perfect.
Next time on the mid-season
finale of Yellowstone..
The greatest threat
to that ranch is our father.
So I will remove the threat.
I got something to ask Kayce.
I need his help.
I need it from all of ya.
Governor Dutton
has violated state law.
The Attorney General's office
is seeking impeachment.
He has declared war upon us.
I'm aware. Beth.
Modify by Blue-Bird™